[{"answer": "It is a fantastic start, Piers.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "From what you understand of what the president will be revealing tomorrow, as what he wants to push forward with, is that enough?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, that remains to be seen.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Can it actually become law?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Is it as shocking as many would have us believe?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Well, this is like Sandy Hook certainly to motivate us to do some reasonable, sensible things that we -- that we must do about gun violence.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Will they just go and find some other weapon that can do the same job for them?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, no one is talking about taking anyone's weapon.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "How do you deal with the Americans who say, no, you're not having any of my guns, it's my Second Amendment right to bear arms, I can have all this?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, listen, I agree with you.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Well, that's not good enough anymore, is it?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Dr. Fox, do you want to jump in here?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, because evil is going to happen.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "But the First Amendment refers to the freedom of expression, on speech and for the press.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Where do we draw the line?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Machine guns were banned in 1934 as a result of the National Firearms Act.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Why -- why ban machine guns then?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, look, the reality is, is that gun sales sigh rocketed upon the election of Barack Obama and Vice President Joe Biden in 2009.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "What does that tell you about -- as a reaction to Aurora and then Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Well, I understand what his position is and it's a little bit of semantics.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "When you hear people say there's just no comparison between, say, the M-16 military weapon and an AR- 15, what is your reaction?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "To protect myself and protect my family.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "What does any civilian need one?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "No, I'm not saying --", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "You believe that an American government in the modern age is going to turn tyrannical?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well, let's look at it right now.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "That you would need an AR-15 to protect yourself against your own government?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "No, the government has a monopoly on legitimate violence.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Government's monopoly on violence?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "To have any gun.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "To have an AR-15?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Because I do want to protect my family.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Why do you need an AR-15?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "You and I agree.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What else do you call it?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "They would find something else.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "The question is, how many would if they didn't have guns in their homes?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "It is not an attack on their rights.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "How do you convince them this is not an attack on their rights, if you like?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "But, Piers, the truth of the matter is this.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "I mean, how are you going to tell my children that nothing has been done after what happened to our family?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "It's really impossible for me to understand that the killers could get that kind of power in their hands.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "When you have a family like this who has been destroyed over what has happened -- you saw, Ashley -- Kendra, when you hear people try to just insist on saying these AR-15 weapons are not assault weapon, what do you say to that?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with this lady about it is our Constitutional right to have -- bear arms.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "When you hear people talk in this way and just have no apparent comprehension, I think, of why you want these kind of weapons taken away, what is your reaction?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "I hope to see a ban on assault rifles or much stricter possession of them.", "docId": "130115pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Do you think he's got it about right?", "qSentId": 652}]